[{"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"C2K": "BC0/BC1", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "unihertz Model": "Luna", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "BLACKVIEW"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "FHD+ 1080x2400", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen,Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Blackview Model": "BV8900", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio P90", "Language": "English", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "itel"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.6", "Display Resolution": "1612x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "New", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52\"", "Display Resolution": "1600*720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"telemoveis": "portable", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "UMIDIGI", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "unihertz"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.81\u201c", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Feature 5": "32MP Front 108MP Rear Smartphone Cellphone Mobile Phones", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "Flip", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS,pse,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.84", "Display Resolution": "2280x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "400", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Xiaomi Model": "6 pro", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.79\"", "Display Resolution": "2460x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 2.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "MIUI 14"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Weight": "198.5g", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "Flip", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi 12", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,20MP,48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4200", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Transparent", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Mi 10 Ultra", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 240 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,8K (4320p) 24 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 865", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MEIZU"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Snapdragon 8 Gen 2"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.55", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "40W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no", "Meizu Model": "20"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Hotwav"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "15000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"4G": "B1/B3/B5/B7/B8/B19/B20", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Hotwav Model": "W10 PRO"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "2640x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Folded Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "10MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Samsung Model": "Galaxy Z Flip 3", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 888", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "K-Touch"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.0", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"SIZE": "145*72.4*9.55mm", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6737M", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Happyhere"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.0", "Display Resolution": "1280x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13.1MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3000-3500 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "MT6735M", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Spredtrum"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "4.0", "Display Resolution": "854x480", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "2MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2350", "Battery Type": "Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G", "NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Battery": "2350mAh Detachable battery", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS,WEEE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Sony"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.2", "Display Resolution": "1920x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "20MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "<3100mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "White/Black/Golden", "Biometrics Technology": "no", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Sony Model": "Z3", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,HD (720p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "German,Polish,French,Norwegian,Turkish,ITALIAN,Spanish,Portuguese,Russian,English,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 801", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Google"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.4", "Display Resolution": "1080x2400", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4300", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card+1 eSIM"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Stormy Black/Sorta Seafoam/Kinda Coral", "Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 240 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "6000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge,Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Dimension": "162.3mm x 77.3mm x 9.6mm", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "redmi 9T", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67", "Display Resolution": "2712x1220", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Other", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "200MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5100", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Others"}, "Connectivity": {"Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi Note 13 Pro", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "9600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "8MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "no", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Motorola"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Dash Charge", "Charging Power": "80W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Google"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Other"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "3120\u00d71440", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,50MP,48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "Other"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5003 mAh", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Chipset": "Google Tensor", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Google Model": "pixel 6 pro", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Google"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.7", "Display Resolution": "1080x2280", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "OLED", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,16MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2400-2800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/White/Orange", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Google Model": "pixel 4", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,4K (2160p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 120 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Refurbished", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 855", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "VIVO"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "2800x1260", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Curved Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "120W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,Spanish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.4", "Display Resolution": "1080x2340", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2227", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Apple Model": "12 mini", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "MEIZU"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.2", "Display Resolution": "3200x1440", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Super AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "20MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 888", "Built in radiator": "no", "Meizu Model": "18"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Huawei"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.95", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2376", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "7000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "22.5W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "HarmonyOS"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Huawei Model": "Enjoy 60X"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "AGM"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.99", "Display Resolution": "2160x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "TFT", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"CDMA": "BC0", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4GHz/5 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "Language": "English,Russian,Arabic", "Qualcomm Model": "Snapdragon 450", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Motorola"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7''", "Display Resolution": "2520x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "2"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Item Condition": "Used", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Origin": "Mainland China"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Motorola"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "qualcomm"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone,5G Mobile Phone,Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Charging 3": "Reverse wired", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "SAMSUNG"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.5", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp,2MP,8MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "no"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Samsung Model": "A32", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "MTK Model": "Dimensity 720 MT6853", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58\u201d", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u2248108MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "\u224832MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "Other", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "65W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G,5 G", "NFC": "YES", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "V30T"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.7", "Display Resolution": "1650x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"telemoveis": "portable", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "UMIDIGI", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.72", "Display Resolution": "2400*1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "90Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperVOOC", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Processor": "MediaTek Helio G88 Octa-core", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "realme model": "C55", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 30 fps,HD (720p) 60 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,EAC", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Infinix"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.67''", "Display Resolution": "2400x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "AMOLED", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "Other", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4500", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"OTG": "Support", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "MTK Model": "Helio G95", "Language": "English,Russian,Spanish,Portuguese"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "2340x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "4", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "13MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Quick Charge 3.0", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Fast Charging Phone"}, "Other": {"Rear Camera": "48MP+8MP+2MP+2MP", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition,Rear-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "NOTE 8", "Battery Capacity Range": "3500-4499 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "ULEFONE"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "1080 x 2408 FHD+", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "\u224864MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "9600", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "33W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Other", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Dock Charging": "Support", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11ac,802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g,802.11a", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "YES", "MTK Model": "Helio G99", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.3", "Display Resolution": "1440x720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Language": "English", "Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "6A", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "DOOGEE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.58", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "32MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "10800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "YES"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "7500+ mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Arabic", "Doogee Model": "S110"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.1", "Display Resolution": "2556x1179px", "Screen Refresh Rate": "120Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "12MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "3200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "YES", "Fast Charging": "USB-PD", "Charging Power": "20W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 eSIM"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Apple Model": "iPhone 14Pro", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.84", "Display Resolution": "2280x1080", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Full Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP,5mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "400", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "18W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Other": {"Xiaomi Model": "REDMI 6 PRO", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "Flip", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UMIDIGI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "Unisoc"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.52", "Display Resolution": "1600*720", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Water Drop Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "2", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "8MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5150", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "": "295369929", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "realme"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.78", "Display Resolution": "1080x2220", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Fullview Display", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "50MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "16MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4800", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "SuperCharge", "Charging Power": "67W"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "In-Screen Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "realme model": "realme 11", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53inch", "Display Resolution": "1600x720", "Screen Refresh Rate": "Other", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Other", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Dedicated slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "no"}, "Other": {"Dimensions": "164.9mm*77mm*9.0mm", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition,Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "10A", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "NONE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MTK Model": "Helio G25", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Apple"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "APPLE"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "5.5", "Display Resolution": "1080x1920", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "12MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2750", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Linghting", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "1 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "IOS"}, "Connectivity": {"NFC": "YES"}, "Other": {"Apple Model": "iPhone 6S Plus", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE,FCC,RoHS", "Item Condition": "Used", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "UNIWA"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "\u22644.0\"", "Display Resolution": "480x320", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "IPS", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "1", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "2000", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "no", "Memory Card Type": "Shared with SIM slot", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES"}, "Other": {"Biometrics Technology": "Face Recognition", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "<3000 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "uniwa Model": "XS12 PRO", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "XIAOMI"}, "Configuration": {"CPU Model": "MTK"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.53", "Display Resolution": "720x1600", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "LCD", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "13MP", "Front Camera Pixel": "5mp"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "4700", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Nonsupport", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Micro USB", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "Memory Card Type": "Not supported", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Resistance": {"IP68/IP69K": "no"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "no", "Bluetooth Version": "YSE", "Wi-fi": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Built-in GPS": "YES", "Other Features": "Photograph Phone"}, "Other": {"Color": "Black/Green/Blue", "Biometrics Technology": "Fingerprint Recognition", "Wi-Fi Transmission Standard": "802.11n 2.4 GHz,802.11b/g", "Design": "BAR", "Xiaomi Model": "Redmi 9A", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Video recording resolution": "FullHD (1080p) 30 fps,FullHD (1080p) 60 fps", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "Used", "MIL-STD-810G": "no", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "no"}}, {"Basic info": {"Brand Name": "Cubot"}, "Display": {"Display Size": "6.583", "Display Resolution": "2408x1080", "Screen Refresh Rate": "60Hz", "Touch Screen": "Yes", "Screen Material": "Other", "Screen Type": "Normal Screen", "Rear Camera Quantity": "3", "Front Camera Quantity": "1"}, "Camera": {"Rear Camera Pixel": "48Mp", "Front Camera Pixel": "24MP"}, "Power": {"Battery Capacity(mAh)": "5200", "Battery Type": "Not Detachable", "Wireless Charging": "no", "Fast Charging": "Adaptive Fast Charge", "Charging Power": "Other"}, "Hardware ports": {"Charging Interface Type": "Type-C", "3.5mm Headphone Port": "YES", "SIM Card Quantity": "2 SIM Card"}, "Systems": {"Operation System": "Android"}, "Connectivity": {"Cellular": "3G,2G,4G", "NFC": "YES"}, "Feature": {"Other Features": "Optical Stabilization,Photograph Phone,Fast Charging Phone,Sports Phone"}, "Other": {"Global Version": "Yes", "Biometrics Technology": "Side-mounted", "Design": "BAR", "Battery Capacity Range": "4500-5999 mAh", "Origin": "Mainland China", "Certification": "CE", "Item Condition": "New", "Language": "English,Russian,German,French,Spanish,Polish,Portuguese,ITALIAN,Turkish,Norwegian,Korean,Japanese,Arabic", "Built in radiator": "YES"}}, {}]